List<Map<String, dynamic>> questions = [
  {
    'question': 'Which IP address belongs to Class A?',
    'answers': ['10.0.0.1', '172.16.0.1', '192.168.1.1', '224.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '10.0.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the default subnet mask for a Class C IP address?',
    'answers': ['255.0.0.0', '255.255.0.0', '255.255.255.0', '255.255.255.255'],
    'correctAnswer': '255.255.255.0'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of the following is a Class B address?',
    'answers': ['10.10.10.10', '172.16.0.1', '192.168.0.1', '224.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '172.16.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which address is used for loopback testing?',
    'answers': ['0.0.0.0', '127.0.0.1', '192.0.2.1', '224.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '127.0.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which IP address belongs to Class C?',
    'answers': ['10.10.10.10', '128.0.0.1', '192.168.0.1', '224.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '192.168.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the default subnet mask for a Class B IP address?',
    'answers': ['255.0.0.0', '255.255.0.0', '255.255.255.0', '255.255.255.255'],
    'correctAnswer': '255.255.0.0'
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following IP addresses is used for private networks?',
    'answers': ['8.8.8.8', '172.16.0.0', '192.0.2.1', '233.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '172.16.0.0'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which IP address is in the range of Class A addresses?',
    'answers': ['130.0.0.1', '200.0.0.1', '12.0.0.1', '230.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '12.0.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which class does the IP address 192.168.1.1 belong to?',
    'answers': ['Class A', 'Class B', 'Class C', 'Class D'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Class C'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of the following is a multicast address?',
    'answers': ['10.10.10.10', '172.16.0.1', '192.168.1.1', '224.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '224.0.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the network address of the IP 172.16.5.10 with a subnet mask of 255.255.252.0?',
    'answers': ['172.16.5.0', '172.16.4.0', '172.16.0.0', '172.16.1.0'],
    'correctAnswer': '172.16.4.0'
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following IP addresses is reserved for experimental purposes?',
    'answers': ['223.255.255.254', '240.0.0.1', '127.0.0.2', '192.168.255.255'],
    'correctAnswer': '240.0.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the highest valid host IP address on the 192.168.1.0/24 network?',
    'answers': [
      '192.168.1.254',
      '192.168.1.255',
      '192.168.1.253',
      '192.168.1.1'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': '192.168.1.254'
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which IP address range is typically used for private networks?',
    'answers': [
      '8.0.0.0 to 8.255.255.255',
      '172.16.0.0 to 172.31.255.255',
      '200.0.0.0 to 200.255.255.255',
      '223.0.0.0 to 223.255.255.255'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': '172.16.0.0 to 172.31.255.255'
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following is a valid broadcast address for a Class B network?',
    'answers': ['172.16.255.255', '172.16.0.0', '172.16.0.1', '172.16.255.0'],
    'correctAnswer': '172.16.255.255'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which IP address belongs to Class E?',
    'answers': [
      '240.0.0.1',
      '10.10.10.10',
      '172.31.255.255',
      '192.168.255.255'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': '240.0.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of the following IP addresses belongs to Class D?',
    'answers': ['198.51.100.14', '239.255.255.254', '128.0.0.1', '192.168.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '239.255.255.254'
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the network address for the IP address 192.168.15.67 with subnet mask 255.255.255.240?',
    'answers': [
      '192.168.15.0',
      '192.168.15.64',
      '192.168.15.32',
      '192.168.15.48'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': '192.168.15.64'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which IP address is a Class B address?',
    'answers': ['10.0.0.1', '128.0.0.1', '191.255.255.255', '192.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '128.0.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the default subnet mask for a Class A IP address?',
    'answers': ['255.255.0.0', '255.255.255.0', '255.0.0.0', '255.255.255.255'],
    'correctAnswer': '255.0.0.0'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of the following IP addresses belongs to Class A?',
    'answers': ['11.0.0.1', '128.0.0.1', '192.168.1.1', '224.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '11.0.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which IP address is used as a loopback address?',
    'answers': ['10.0.0.1', '127.0.0.1', '192.168.0.1', '224.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '127.0.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of the following IP addresses is a multicast address?',
    'answers': ['10.10.10.10', '172.16.0.1', '192.168.1.1', '224.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '224.0.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the default subnet mask for a Class C IP address?',
    'answers': ['255.0.0.0', '255.255.0.0', '255.255.255.0', '255.255.255.255'],
    'correctAnswer': '255.255.255.0'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of the following IP addresses is a Class B address?',
    'answers': ['10.0.0.1', '172.16.0.1', '192.168.1.1', '224.0.0.1'],
    'correctAnswer': '172.16.0.1'
  },
  {
    'question':
        'What is the network address for the IP address 10.10.10.10 with subnet mask 255.255.255.0?',
    'answers': ['10.10.10.0', '10.10.10.1', '10.10.0.0', '10.0.0.0'],
    'correctAnswer': '10.10.10.0'
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the default port number for HTTP?',
    'answers': ['21', '80', '443', '22'],
    'correctAnswer': '80'
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which protocol is used to send emails?',
    'answers': ['SMTP', 'FTP', 'HTTP', 'SNMP'],
    'correctAnswer': 'SMTP'
  },
  {
    'question': 'What does the acronym DNS stand for?',
    'answers': [
      'Domain Network System',
      'Dynamic Network System',
      'Domain Name System',
      'Dynamic Name System'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Domain Name System'
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the function of a router?',
    'answers': [
      'To filter traffic based on IP addresses',
      'To connect multiple networks and forward packets between them',
      'To convert analog signals to digital signals',
      'To store and retrieve files'
    ],
    'correctAnswer':
        'To connect multiple networks and forward packets between them'
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the maximum length of a MAC address?',
    'answers': ['32 bits', '48 bits', '64 bits', '128 bits'],
    'correctAnswer': '48 bits'
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which layer of the OSI model is responsible for error detection and correction?',
    'answers': [
      'Network layer',
      'Data link layer',
      'Transport layer',
      'Session layer'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Data link layer'
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the purpose of a subnet mask in networking?',
    'answers': [
      'To identify the default gateway',
      'To identify the host portion of an IP address',
      'To identify the network portion of an IP address',
      'To identify the DNS server'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'To identify the network portion of an IP address'
  }
];

List<Map<String, dynamic>> asciiquestions = [
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii decimal code for the uppercase letter 'A'?",
    'answers': ['74', '65', '90', '66'],
    'correctAnswer': '65'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ASCII code for the letter 'P'?",
    'answers': ['77', '78', '79', '80'],
    'correctAnswer': '80'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the lowercase letter 'q'?",
    'answers': ['115', '120', '113', '178'],
    'correctAnswer': '113'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the value for the letter 'C'?",
    'answers': ['67', '27', '97', '77'],
    'correctAnswer': '67'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code corresponds to the letter 'D'?",
    'answers': ['25', '78', '69', '68'],
    'correctAnswer': '68'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which ascii code corresponds to the letter 'j'?",
    'answers': ['106', '107', '108', '109'],
    'correctAnswer': '106'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii value for the letter 'Q'?",
    'answers': ['113', '81', '34', '119'],
    'correctAnswer': '81'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which ascii code corresponds to the letter 't'?",
    'answers': ['120', '116', '150', '112'],
    'correctAnswer': '116'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which ascii code represents the digit '2'?",
    'answers': ['40', '50', '60', '70'],
    'correctAnswer': '50'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which ascii code stands for the digit '9'?",
    'answers': ['97', '54', '57', '21'],
    'correctAnswer': '57'
  },
  {
    'question': "What decimal ascii code represents the symbol '&'?",
    'answers': ['49', '38', '88', '97'],
    'correctAnswer': '38'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which ascii code corresponds to the symbol '%'?",
    'answers': ['37', '27', '85', '77'],
    'correctAnswer': '37'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii value for the symbol?",
    'answers': ['36', '37', '38', '39'],
    'correctAnswer': '36'
  },
  {
    'question': "What ascii code for the symbol '@'?",
    'answers': ['88', '99', '64', '56'],
    'correctAnswer': '64'
  },
  {
    'question': "What decimal ascii code represents the digit '7'?",
    'answers': ['55', '56', '57', '58'],
    'correctAnswer': '55'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii value for the symbol '+'?",
    'answers': ['44', '43', '38', '22'],
    'correctAnswer': '43'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which ascii code represents the symbol ','?",
    'answers': ['44', '45', '46', '47'],
    'correctAnswer': '44'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which ascii code corresponds to the symbols '*'?",
    'answers': ['43', '42', '41', '44'],
    'correctAnswer': '42'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which decimal ascii code represents the symbols '?'?",
    'answers': ['63', '65', '62', '60'],
    'correctAnswer': '63'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which ascii code represents the symbol '/'?",
    'answers': ['49', '47', '50', '67'],
    'correctAnswer': '47'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code correspond to the letter 's'?",
    'answers': ['112', '76', '109', '115'],
    'correctAnswer': '115'
  },
  {
    'question': "What character represents ascii code letter 'W'?",
    'answers': ['84', '87', '88', '79'],
    'correctAnswer': '87'
  },
  {
    'question': "What decimal ascii code represents the digit '5'?",
    'answers': ['60', '55', '53', '48'],
    'correctAnswer': '53'
  },
  {
    'question': "What decimal ascii code represents the digit '0'?",
    'answers': ['49', '48', '50', '62'],
    'correctAnswer': '48'
  },
  {
    'question': "What character the ascii code corresponds to the letter 'Z'?",
    'answers': ['89', '90', '91', '92'],
    'correctAnswer': '90'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which character ascii code represents the 'm'?",
    'answers': ['110', '108', '109', '120'],
    'correctAnswer': '109'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which ascii code corresponds to the letter 'd'?",
    'answers': ['19', '97', '99', '89'],
    'correctAnswer': '97'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the symbol ';'?",
    'answers': ['58', '59', '60', '61'],
    'correctAnswer': '59'
  },
  {
    'question': "What ascii code correspond to the number '3'?",
    'answers': ['50', '40', '41', '51'],
    'correctAnswer': '51'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the letter 'J'?",
    'answers': ['64', '74', '84', '94'],
    'correctAnswer': '74'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the letter 'H'?",
    'answers': ['1001001', '01010000', '10010000', '01001000'],
    'correctAnswer': '01001000'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the digit '3'?",
    'answers': ['1100011', '00110011', '100011', '011001'],
    'correctAnswer': '00110011'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the character represent ascii code 'V'?",
    'answers': ['1001010', '00100101', '01010110', '1010110'],
    'correctAnswer': '01010110'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the symbol '~'?",
    'answers': ['10110101', '01111110', '10000100', '01010111'],
    'correctAnswer': '01111110'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the symbol '@'?",
    'answers': ['01100010', '00111100', '01000000', '10100000'],
    'correctAnswer': '01000000'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the letter 'U'?",
    'answers': ['01010101', '01110101', '11010101', '0110101'],
    'correctAnswer': '01010101'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the digit '4'?",
    'answers': ['00100100', '1100100', '0110100', '1000100'],
    'correctAnswer': '0110100'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the symbol ')'",
    'answers': ['0101000', '10010101', '00101010', '01011001'],
    'correctAnswer': '01011001'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code character of 'X'?",
    'answers': ['0101101', '1011000', '10010101', '01011000'],
    'correctAnswer': '01011000'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code symbol of '+'?",
    'answers': ['0101011', '11010101', '10100000', '00101011'],
    'correctAnswer': '00101011'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the symbol ?",
    'answers': ['1001000', '1101001', '01000011', '00100100'],
    'correctAnswer': '00100100'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the letter 'z'?",
    'answers': ['1100110', '01011010', '1100101', '00111010'],
    'correctAnswer': '01011010'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the letter 'A'?",
    'answers': ['1000001', '01000001', '1100001', '00100001'],
    'correctAnswer': '01000001'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the digit '5'?",
    'answers': ['01000101', '1100101', '00110101', '1000101'],
    'correctAnswer': '00110101'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the symbol '#'?",
    'answers': ['00100011', '01000011', '01110000', '1100011'],
    'correctAnswer': '00100011'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the symbol of 'space'?",
    'answers': ['01101100', '00101001', '00100000', '00111011'],
    'correctAnswer': '00100000'
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the ascii code for the symbol of ':'?",
    'answers': ['00111010', '00101100', '01110000', '01110001'],
    'correctAnswer': '00111010'
  },
  {
    'question': "Which binary code represents the ASCII character 'F'?",
    'answers': ['01000110', '10000110', '11000110', '00100010'],
    'correctAnswer': '01000110'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "Which of the following binary sequences corresponds to the ASCII character '3'?",
    'answers': ['10000110', '01100011', '00110011', '11110011'],
    'correctAnswer': '00110011'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "Which of the following is the binary representation of the ASCII character '5'?",
    'answers': ['01100101', '01010000', '00110101', '10101010'],
    'correctAnswer': '00110101'
  },
];

List<Map<String, dynamic>> numbersystemsquestions = [
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 101 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['2', '5', '7', '8'],
    'correctAnswer': '5'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 111 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['7', '9', '10', '6'],
    'correctAnswer': '7'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 10000 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['12', '13', '16', '15'],
    'correctAnswer': '16'
  },
  {
    'question': "CONVERT THE DECIMAL NUMBER 3 INTO BINARY. (DECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['10', '101', '110', '11'],
    'correctAnswer': '11'
  },
  {
    'question': "CONVERT THE DECIMAL NUMBER 10 INTO BINARY. (DECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['1100', '1011', '1010', '1110'],
    'correctAnswer': '1010'
  },
  {
    'question': "CONVERT THE DECIMAL NUMBER 9 INTO BINARY. (DECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['1001', '1111', '1010', '1110'],
    'correctAnswer': '1001'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 111 TO ITS OCTAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – OCTAL)",
    'answers': ['7', '9', '8', '6'],
    'correctAnswer': '7'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 1011 TO ITS OCTAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – OCTAL)",
    'answers': ['11', '10', '12', '13'],
    'correctAnswer': '11'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 1000 TO ITS OCTAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – OCTAL)",
    'answers': ['11', '10', '12', '13'],
    'correctAnswer': '10'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE OCTAL NUMBER 3 TO ITS BINARY EQUIVALENT. (OCTAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['11', '10', '100', '101'],
    'correctAnswer': '11'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE OCTAL NUMBER 14 TO ITS BINARY EQUIVALENT. (OCTAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['111', '101', '1100', '1010'],
    'correctAnswer': '1100'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 1001 TO ITS HEXADECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – HEXADECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['11', '10', '9', '13'],
    'correctAnswer': '9'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 1100 TO ITS HEXADECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – HEXADECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['9', 'A', 'B', 'C'],
    'correctAnswer': 'C'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE HEXADECIMAL NUMBER 9 TO ITS BINARY EQUIVALENT. (HEXADECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['111', '1001', '1100', '1010'],
    'correctAnswer': '1001'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE HEXADECIMAL NUMBER 2 TO ITS BINARY EQUIVALENT. (HEXADECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['0', '1', '11', '10'],
    'correctAnswer': '10'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 11111 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['21', '31', '32', '30'],
    'correctAnswer': '31'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 11110 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['33', '32', '30', '31'],
    'correctAnswer': '30'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 101000 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['42', '43', '41', '40'],
    'correctAnswer': '40'
  },
  {
    'question': "CONVERT THE DECIMAL NUMBER 47 INTO BINARY. (DECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['101111', '101101', '110111', '100001'],
    'correctAnswer': '101111'
  },
  {
    'question': "CONVERT THE DECIMAL NUMBER 55 INTO BINARY. (DECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['101111', '101101', '110111', '110111'],
    'correctAnswer': '110111'
  },
  {
    'question': "CONVERT THE DECIMAL NUMBER 41 INTO BINARY. (DECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['100100', '111111', '101001', '111000'],
    'correctAnswer': '101001'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 100000 TO ITS OCTAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – OCTAL)",
    'answers': ['40', '41', '39', '42'],
    'correctAnswer': '40'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 11100 TO ITS OCTAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – OCTAL)",
    'answers': ['33', '34', '35', '36'],
    'correctAnswer': '34'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 10111 TO ITS OCTAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – OCTAL)",
    'answers': ['25', '26', '27', '28'],
    'correctAnswer': '27'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE OCTAL NUMBER 37 TO ITS BINARY EQUIVALENT. (OCTAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['11010', '10000', '10011', '11111'],
    'correctAnswer': '11111'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE OCTAL NUMBER 25 TO ITS BINARY EQUIVALENT. (OCTAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['11101', '10101', '11000', '10100'],
    'correctAnswer': '10101'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 11010 TO ITS HEXADECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – HEXADECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['1A', '19', '1B', '1C'],
    'correctAnswer': '1A'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 10001 TO ITS HEXADECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – HEXADECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['11', '10', 'F', 'E'],
    'correctAnswer': '11'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE HEXADECIMAL NUMBER 1C TO ITS BINARY EQUIVALENT. (HEXADECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['11100', '10011', '11001', '10101'],
    'correctAnswer': '11100'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE HEXADECIMAL NUMBER 1F TO ITS BINARY EQUIVALENT. (HEXADECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['10101', '11100', '11111', '11110'],
    'correctAnswer': '11111'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 110000 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['49', '50', '48', '47'],
    'correctAnswer': '48'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 111111 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['63', '62', '61', '60'],
    'correctAnswer': '63'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 1000101 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['65', '67', '69', '71'],
    'correctAnswer': '69'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 1100100 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['100', '107', '103', '105'],
    'correctAnswer': '100'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE DECIMAL NUMBER 111 INTO BINARY. (DECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['1110000', '1110001', '1101111', '1101101'],
    'correctAnswer': '1101111'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 1011110 TO ITS OCTAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – OCTAL)",
    'answers': ['94', '96', '99', '95'],
    'correctAnswer': '94'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE OCTAL NUMBER 132 TO ITS BINARY EQUIVALENT. (OCTAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['1011100', '1011111', '1011010', '1011011'],
    'correctAnswer': '1011010'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 1111110 TO ITS HEXADECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – HEXADECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['7B', '7C', '7D', '7E'],
    'correctAnswer': '7C'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 110000 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['48', '49', '50', '47'],
    'correctAnswer': '48'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 111111 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['63', '62', '61', '60'],
    'correctAnswer': '63'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 1000101 TO ITS DECIMAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – DECIMAL)",
    'answers': ['69', '65', '67', '71'],
    'correctAnswer': '69'
  },
  {
    'question': "CONVERT THE DECIMAL NUMBER 60 INTO BINARY. (DECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['111100', '101111', '110111', '101101'],
    'correctAnswer': '111100'
  },
  {
    'question': "CONVERT THE DECIMAL NUMBER 67 INTO BINARY. (DECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['1000011', '1011110', '1101110', '1011011'],
    'correctAnswer': '1000011'
  },
  {
    'question': "CONVERT THE DECIMAL NUMBER 79 INTO BINARY. (DECIMAL – BINARY)",
    'answers': ['1001111', '1010011', '1111110', '1110001'],
    'correctAnswer': '1001111'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 111111 TO ITS OCTAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – OCTAL)",
    'answers': ['77', '74', '75', '76'],
    'correctAnswer': '77'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 110110 TO ITS OCTAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – OCTAL)",
    'answers': ['66', '62', '65', '64'],
    'correctAnswer': '66'
  },
  {
    'question':
        "CONVERT THE BINARY NUMBER 1000000 TO ITS OCTAL EQUIVALENT. (BINARY – OCTAL)",
    'answers': ['100', '101', '102', '103'],
    'correctAnswer': '100'
  }
];

List<Map<String, dynamic>> arithmeticQuestions = [
  {
    'question': "10 + 5 =",
    'answers': ['14', '15', '16', '17'],
    'correctAnswer': '15'
  },
  {
    'question': "15 + 8 =",
    'answers': ['22', '23', '24', '25'],
    'correctAnswer': '23'
  },
  {
    'question': "20 + 4 =",
    'answers': ['22', '23', '24', '25'],
    'correctAnswer': '24'
  },
  {
    'question': "22 + 6 =",
    'answers': ['28', '29', '30', '31'],
    'correctAnswer': '28'
  },
  {
    'question': "26 + 4 =",
    'answers': ['29', '30', '31', '32'],
    'correctAnswer': '30'
  },
  {
    'question': "13 + 7 =",
    'answers': ['19', '20', '21', '22'],
    'correctAnswer': '20'
  },
  {
    'question': "30 + 5 =",
    'answers': ['34', '35', '36', '37'],
    'correctAnswer': '35'
  },
  {
    'question': "14 + 11 =",
    'answers': ['24', '25', '26', '27'],
    'correctAnswer': '25'
  },
  {
    'question': "28 + 2 =",
    'answers': ['30', '29', '28', '27'],
    'correctAnswer': '30'
  },
  {
    'question': "7 + 3 =",
    'answers': ['10', '11', '12', '13'],
    'correctAnswer': '10'
  },
  {
    'question': "6 + 9 =",
    'answers': ['15', '16', '17', '18'],
    'correctAnswer': '15'
  },
  {
    'question': "17 + 8 =",
    'answers': ['23', '24', '25', '26'],
    'correctAnswer': '25'
  },
  {
    'question': "15 - 8 =",
    'answers': ['5', '6', '7', '8'],
    'correctAnswer': '7'
  },
  {
    'question': "25 - 6 =",
    'answers': ['19', '18', '17', '16'],
    'correctAnswer': '19'
  },
  {
    'question': "18 - 9 =",
    'answers': ['8', '9', '10', '11'],
    'correctAnswer': '9'
  },
  {
    'question': "30 - 14 =",
    'answers': ['14', '15', '16', '17'],
    'correctAnswer': '16'
  },
  {
    'question': "27 - 12 =",
    'answers': ['13', '14', '15', '16'],
    'correctAnswer': '15'
  },
  {
    'question': "22 - 7 =",
    'answers': ['14', '15', '16', '17'],
    'correctAnswer': '15'
  },
  {
    'question': "31 - 16 =",
    'answers': ['14', '15', '16', '17'],
    'correctAnswer': '15'
  },
  {
    'question': "20 - 3 =",
    'answers': ['17', '18', '19', '20'],
    'correctAnswer': '17'
  },
  {
    'question': "12 x 11 =",
    'answers': ['132', '122', '112', '142'],
    'correctAnswer': '132'
  },
  {
    'question': "17 x 15 =",
    'answers': ['255', '265', '275', '285'],
    'correctAnswer': '255'
  },
  {
    'question': "23 x 14 =",
    'answers': ['312', '322', '332', '342'],
    'correctAnswer': '322'
  },
  {
    'question': "36 x 18 =",
    'answers': ['648', '658', '668', '678'],
    'correctAnswer': '648'
  },
  {
    'question': "42 x 27 =",
    'answers': ['1134', '1144', '1154', '1164'],
    'correctAnswer': '1134'
  },
  {
    'question': "51 x 19 =",
    'answers': ['969', '979', '989', '999'],
    'correctAnswer': '969'
  },
  {
    'question': "64 x 13 =",
    'answers': ['822', '842', '852', '832'],
    'correctAnswer': '832'
  },
  {
    'question': "88 x 22 =",
    'answers': ['1926', '1946', '1956', '1936'],
    'correctAnswer': '1936'
  },
  {
    'question': "79 x 15 =",
    'answers': ['1175', '1185', '1195', '1205'],
    'correctAnswer': '1185'
  },
  {
    'question': "132 ÷ 12 =",
    'answers': ['10', '11', '12', '13'],
    'correctAnswer': '11'
  },
  {
    'question': "315 ÷ 21 =",
    'answers': ['15', '14', '16', '17'],
    'correctAnswer': '15'
  },
  {
    'question': "864 ÷ 24 =",
    'answers': ['34', '35', '36', '37'],
    'correctAnswer': '36'
  },
  {
    'question': "420 ÷ 20 =",
    'answers': ['20', '21', '22', '23'],
    'correctAnswer': '21'
  },
  {
    'question': "357 ÷ 17 =",
    'answers': ['20', '22', '23', '21'],
    'correctAnswer': '21'
  },
  {
    'question': "625 ÷ 25 =",
    'answers': ['23', '24', '25', '26'],
    'correctAnswer': '25'
  },
  {
    'question': "12 + (7+8) x 5 =",
    'answers': ['85', '86', '87', '88'],
    'correctAnswer': '87'
  },
  {
    'question': "4 x (15 - 13) + 16 =",
    'answers': ['24', '25', '26', '27'],
    'correctAnswer': '24'
  },
  {
    'question': "12 x 3 + (100 ÷10) =",
    'answers': ['43', '44', '45', '46'],
    'correctAnswer': '46'
  },
  {
    'question': "(9 -2) + (3 x 10) + 7 =",
    'answers': ['43', '44', '45', '46'],
    'correctAnswer': '44'
  },
  {
    'question': "(93 + 7) x 6 + 10 =",
    'answers': ['610', '620', '630', '640'],
    'correctAnswer': '610'
  },
  {
    'question': "6 + 7 x 8 =",
    'answers': ['104', '62', '22', '108'],
    'correctAnswer': '62'
  },
  {
    'question': "8 ÷ 2 (5 + 16) - 6 =",
    'answers': ['118', '19', '60', '30'],
    'correctAnswer': '118'
  },
  {
    'question': "3 + 6 x (5 + 4) ÷ 3 =",
    'answers': ['16', '12', '21', '61'],
    'correctAnswer': '21'
  },
  {
    'question': "9 + 3 x (8 + 7) + 9 =",
    'answers': ['45', '36', '49', '35'],
    'correctAnswer': '45'
  },
  {
    'question': "20 - 4 + 6 x 3 =",
    'answers': ['66', '34', '2', '10'],
    'correctAnswer': '34'
  },
  {
    'question': "37 + 3 x 2 ÷ 6 =",
    'answers': ['13', '7', '46', '38'],
    'correctAnswer': '38'
  },
  {
    'question': "24 x 6 - 2 + 5 x 2 =",
    'answers': ['152', '294', '142', '249'],
    'correctAnswer': '152'
  },
  {
    'question': "82 + 9 x 9 + 20 =",
    'answers': ['839', '183', '389', '381'],
    'correctAnswer': '183'
  },
  {
    'question': "36 - 6 x 5 =",
    'answers': ['150', '100', '6', '9'],
    'correctAnswer': '6'
  },
  {
    'question': "4 x (8 x 5) + 17 =",
    'answers': ['177', '157', '167', '187'],
    'correctAnswer': '177'
  },
  {
    'question': "36 - 6 x 5 =",
    'answers': ['150', '100', '6', '9'],
    'correctAnswer': '6'
  },
  {
    'question': "4 x (8 x 5) + 17 =",
    'answers': ['177', '157', '167', '187'],
    'correctAnswer': '177'
  },
  {
    'question': "9 x 8 - 5 =",
    'answers': ['71', '67', '68', '69'],
    'correctAnswer': '67'
  },
  {
    'question': "15 ÷ 3 + 4 =",
    'answers': ['8', '9', '10', '11'],
    'correctAnswer': '9'
  },
  {
    'question': "18 ÷ 2 x 3 =",
    'answers': ['18', '20', '21', '22'],
    'correctAnswer': '27'
  },
  {
    'question': "24 - 8 ÷ 2 =",
    'answers': ['20', '18', '16', '14'],
    'correctAnswer': '20'
  },
  {
    'question': "7 + 4 x 3 =",
    'answers': ['19', '21', '23', '25'],
    'correctAnswer': '19'
  },
  {
    'question': "10 x 6 ÷ 5 =",
    'answers': ['12', '11', '10', '9'],
    'correctAnswer': '12'
  },
  {
    'question': "45 ÷ 9 + 2 =",
    'answers': ['6', '7', '8', '9'],
    'correctAnswer': '7'
  },
  {
    'question': "20 - 4 x 2 =",
    'answers': ['12', '14', '16', '18'],
    'correctAnswer': '12'
  },
  {
    'question': "5 x (7 + 3) =",
    'answers': ['50', '40', '30', '20'],
    'correctAnswer': '50'
  },
  {
    'question': "25 ÷ 5 x 4 =",
    'answers': ['20', '16', '12', '8'],
    'correctAnswer': '20'
  },
  {
    'question': "12 + 3 x 4 =",
    'answers': ['15', '24', '36', '48'],
    'correctAnswer': '24'
  },
  {
    'question': "30 ÷ 5 + 6 =",
    'answers': ['11', '12', '13', '14'],
    'correctAnswer': '12'
  },
  {
    'question': "18 - 2 x 5 =",
    'answers': ['8', '6', '4', '2'],
    'correctAnswer': '8'
  },
  {
    'question': "9 + 4 x 2 =",
    'answers': ['13', '17', '21', '25'],
    'correctAnswer': '17'
  },
  {
    'question': "40 ÷ 8 + 3 =",
    'answers': ['7', '8', '9', '10'],
    'correctAnswer': '8'
  },
  {
    'question': "15 - 3 x 2 =",
    'answers': ['9', '11', '13', '15'],
    'correctAnswer': '9'
  },
  {
    'question': "6 x 5 ÷ 2 =",
    'answers': ['12', '13', '14', '15'],
    'correctAnswer': '15'
  },
  {
    'question': "28 ÷ 7 + 3 =",
    'answers': ['7', '8', '9', '10'],
    'correctAnswer': '7'
  }
];

List<Map<String, dynamic>> romannumeralsquestions = [
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 1?",
    "options": ["I", "V", "X", "L"],
    "answer": "I"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 2?",
    "options": ["II", "III", "IV", "V"],
    "answer": "II"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 3?",
    "options": ["II", "III", "IV", "V"],
    "answer": "III"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 4?",
    "options": ["IV", "V", "VI", "IX"],
    "answer": "IV"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 5?",
    "options": ["V", "IX", "X", "L"],
    "answer": "V"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 6?",
    "options": ["VI", "VII", "VIII", "IX"],
    "answer": "VI"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 7?",
    "options": ["VII", "VIII", "IX", "X"],
    "answer": "VII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 8?",
    "options": ["VIII", "IX", "X", "XI"],
    "answer": "VIII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 9?",
    "options": ["IX", "X", "XI", "XII"],
    "answer": "IX"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 10?",
    "options": ["X", "XI", "XII", "XIII"],
    "answer": "X"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 11?",
    "options": ["XI", "XII", "XIII", "XIV"],
    "answer": "XI"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 12?",
    "options": ["XII", "XIII", "XIV", "XV"],
    "answer": "XII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 13?",
    "options": ["XIII", "XIV", "XV", "XVI"],
    "answer": "XIII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 14?",
    "options": ["XIV", "XV", "XVI", "XVII"],
    "answer": "XIV"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 15?",
    "options": ["XV", "XVI", "XVII", "XVIII"],
    "answer": "XV"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 16?",
    "options": ["XVI", "XVII", "XVIII", "XIX"],
    "answer": "XVI"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 17?",
    "options": ["XVII", "XVIII", "XIX", "XX"],
    "answer": "XVII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 18?",
    "options": ["XVIII", "XIX", "XX", "XXI"],
    "answer": "XVIII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 19?",
    "options": ["XIX", "XX", "XXI", "XXII"],
    "answer": "XIX"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 20?",
    "options": ["XX", "XXI", "XXII", "XXIII"],
    "answer": "XX"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 21?",
    "options": ["XXI", "XXII", "XXIII", "XXIV"],
    "answer": "XXI"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 22?",
    "options": ["XXII", "XXIII", "XXIV", "XXV"],
    "answer": "XXII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 23?",
    "options": ["XXIII", "XXIV", "XXV", "XXVI"],
    "answer": "XXIII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 24?",
    "options": ["XXIV", "XXV", "XXVI", "XXVII"],
    "answer": "XXIV"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 25?",
    "options": ["XXV", "XXVI", "XXVII", "XXVIII"],
    "answer": "XXV"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 26?",
    "options": ["XXVI", "XXVII", "XXVIII", "XXIX"],
    "answer": "XXVI"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 27?",
    "options": ["XXVII", "XXVIII", "XXIX", "XXX"],
    "answer": "XXVII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 28?",
    "options": ["XXVIII", "XXIX", "XXX", "XXXI"],
    "answer": "XXVIII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 29?",
    "options": ["XXIX", "XXX", "XXXI", "XXXII"],
    "answer": "XXIX"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 30?",
    "options": ["XXX", "XXXI", "XXXII", "XXXIII"],
    "answer": "XXX"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 31?",
    "options": ["XXXI", "XXXII", "XXXIII", "XXXIV"],
    "answer": "XXXI"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 32?",
    "options": ["XXXII", "XXXIII", "XXXIV", "XXXV"],
    "answer": "XXXII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 33?",
    "options": ["XXXIII", "XXXIV", "XXXV", "XXXVI"],
    "answer": "XXXIII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 34?",
    "options": ["XXXIV", "XXXV", "XXXVI", "XXXVII"],
    "answer": "XXXIV"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 35?",
    "options": ["XXXV", "XXXVI", "XXXVII", "XXXVIII"],
    "answer": "XXXV"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 36?",
    "options": ["XXXVI", "XXXVII", "XXXVIII", "XXXIX"],
    "answer": "XXXVI"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 37?",
    "options": ["XXXVII", "XXXVIII", "XXXIX", "XL"],
    "answer": "XXXVII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 38?",
    "options": ["XXXVIII", "XXXIX", "XL", "XLI"],
    "answer": "XXXVIII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 39?",
    "options": ["XXXIX", "XL", "XLI", "XLII"],
    "answer": "XXXIX"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 40?",
    "options": ["XL", "XLI", "XLII", "XLIII"],
    "answer": "XL"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 41?",
    "options": ["XLI", "XLII", "XLIII", "XLIV"],
    "answer": "XLI"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 42?",
    "options": ["XLII", "XLIII", "XLIV", "XLV"],
    "answer": "XLII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 43?",
    "options": ["XLIII", "XLIV", "XLV", "XLVI"],
    "answer": "XLIII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 44?",
    "options": ["XLIV", "XLV", "XLVI", "XLVII"],
    "answer": "XLIV"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 45?",
    "options": ["XLV", "XLVI", "XLVII", "XLVIII"],
    "answer": "XLV"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 46?",
    "options": ["XLVI", "XLVII", "XLVIII", "XLIX"],
    "answer": "XLVI"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 47?",
    "options": ["XLVII", "XLVIII", "XLIX", "L"],
    "answer": "XLVII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 48?",
    "options": ["XLVIII", "XLIX", "L", "LI"],
    "answer": "XLVIII"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 49?",
    "options": ["XLIX", "L", "LI", "LII"],
    "answer": "XLIX"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for 50?",
    "options": ["L", "LI", "LII", "LIII"],
    "answer": "L"
  },
];
